Hello everybody.
We're Ukka.
I'm Ruri Aoi.
I'm Koharu Wakana
I'm Yu Miyazawa.
I'm Rina.
I'm Moa Seirizawa
I'm Sora Akane
I'm Riju Murahoshi
I look forward to working with you.
So, this time
It will be a collaboration project.
This is a collaboration project.
Wait a minute!
A YouTuber?
Yay!
Ima Lynn!
No, no, no, no!
We've decided on a collaboration project!
Who will we collaborate with this time?
Mr. Shuma!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Once before.
Two years ago, when TATYUNA did an all-art live show
I had a chance to do a talk with one of the members.
I was asked to say "Yay" when I got into the mood.
to get into the spirit of the event.
I got it from Mr. Shuma.
Since then, we've always said "Yay" when we get into the spirit of the show.
I still do it to this day.
and then we start the live performance.
I don't remember.
Why?
About two years ago.
I'm taking good care of that guy.
You take care of him.
I just don't remember.
I'm sorry for what I did for you.
He's like this.
I'm just a normal guy.
I'd like to work with you, Mr. Shima.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Today...
I've already decided on a few things, but I'd like to know the fortune of the group and the ranking of the fortune in 2025. I'd also like to know who will be the key person in the year 2025.
Yes, sir.
You know, you're not involved in our lives.
I don't know...
That's interesting.
It's a difference in intensity.
It's not warm yet.
Shall we do it together?
I'm sure we've done that once before.
There's something I've always done. I'll teach you.
Teach me.
Yes, it's called "speed up time".
It's called "speed-up time.
I, Rina, Yu, Koaruchan, Ruri, Rizu, Sora, and Shuma, in that order, say the highest peak.
I want you to say it with a higher tension than the person in front of us.
Wait a minute, I want to be first.
I'd like you to be last there.
In other words.
I want you to say "guchou.
I don't know, it's kind of high on the nose.
This is as far as I'll go.
I'll go with my spirit.
And after that
Yay!
Up to here
I'd like to have some of Shinwa-san's
That's it.
It's 5:30 in the morning.
No, no, no.
Why do you have it?
It's midday.
It's totally daytime.
Here we go.
High tide.
Highest tide.
High tide!
Highest Tide
Ukka
The highest tide.
Vuka! Vuka!
Yeah!
It's done!
It felt good.
How was it?
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Are you warmed up?
No, I'm not warmed up at all.
What?
I'm not warm. Shall we go?
Yes, sir!
Yes, please, sir. Please.
Please, please, please.
Please.
Okay, then.
Let's go to the group.
Ukka.
Actually, you know what?
I've been consulting on a case I've been trying to figure out.
You want to know about this?
Are you sure you're okay?
I've been working on it.
You didn't know, did you?
I didn't know.
When they were trying to figure out the "wocka" word.
In the back.
I was looking at the stroke counts.
You know what?
Really.
No, time is flying.
It was like a shocking fact, but it is.
So, the strokes themselves, Ukka, are very good strokes.
Thank you very much.
So, I dropped "ukka" into katakana once,
And then we take out the stroke count from there.
So, it becomes "Hakkaku".
So, the theme is to sell steadily, carefully, and slowly,
So, it is not about selling in a hurry or achieving something in a hurry.
It's no good if you try to sell in a hurry or achieve something in a hurry, isn't it?
Hmmm.
So, if you are really steady, careful, and steady,
It will come sooner or later, won't it? I guess.
Hmmm...
Yes.
I don't know, this...
Hmm.
I wonder, is it this school teacher?
Ha-ha-ha.
Well, I've never tried anything like this before,
And things I'm not good at, respectively.
Yeah.
This is the year to challenge them individually.
What are you not good at?
What are you not good at? Food?
Anything.
Green peppers?
I'd like to learn to eat bell peppers.
Even if you have to cook it in different ways, you can learn to eat it.
It really doesn't matter what it is, just conquer one of your weaknesses.
If you can't overcome it, don't do it.
Oh, on the contrary.
What!
I'll take up the challenge.
I'll take on challenges, but if it becomes too much for me, I can stop. But if there is a possibility that we can improve our ability or that of Ukka by continuing, it is better for Ukka to keep on trying.
In terms of overall luck and fortune, the year 2026 will be better than 2025.
In terms of overall luck and fortune, the year 2026 is more likely than the year 2025 to start running at full speed.
In 2026, he said, he will be running at a high speed.
In 2026, we will be in a position to ride on our own current.
So, in 2025, I will be able to consolidate myself and build up my abilities.
and to overcome some of my weaknesses.
It will be a very important point for you.
So it is important to be aware of this.
So, the theme for 2025 is to be aware of this and take action.
Okay, let's continue.
Okay.
Are you ready to go?
I'm going.
You know, rankings aren't supposed to be attached.
No.
Well, they should be.
What's that?
Your friends want me to put it on.
Who is it?
Who was it?
Who?
Luck.
There's no good or bad. The Ryukyu Feng Shui way of looking at it is...
Just like nature. Just like the seasons.
Spring is not number one, is it?
Sure. Summer is the way to live in summer.
Spring has its own way of spending spring, and winter has its own way of spending winter.
It's called luck. And if you go against luck...
What happens if you turn up the heat in the summer? What happens if you do that?
You'll get heat stroke, you'll get sick, you'll get sick, so there are different ways to spend your time, so if you follow them, basically you'll be fine.
Okay. Okay, so where do you want to start? No. 6?
I'm sorry, let's start with number 6.
I knew you'd do it this way.
Okay, let's start. The sixth one is...
Aoi, the 6th place.
Well...
If we talk about luck, she has a chance to be No.1, and a chance to be No.6.
And there's a chance that you'll be at the bottom.
So it's both.
It's going to be a year that you can't read at all.
So one of the themes that we talked about a little bit earlier is.
You really should be able to eat bell peppers.
And then there's the image change.
Change your hairstyle.
Change the way you dress.
Or change the way you wear your clothes, or the way you put on your makeup.
or change the way you dress or the way you do your makeup
I think it will go in the right direction.
Yes, I think so.
That's what I'm thinking.
So, let's change our image and eat green peppers, shall we?
Green peppers?
I can eat green peppers.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Lulie didn't tell me.
Oh, no!
But if you start eating green peppers.
I mean, there's a chance you'll be number one.
That's what I mean.
I'll do my best. Bell peppers.
Next year, in 2025...
Which group should we go for?
Which one?
Oh, this one?
Now, of course, I'll be able to eat it.
But I want to make 2025 the year that I can challenge other things
I want to make it to 2025.
And I might even cut my hair.
Oh, cut it off?
That's too much.
It's going to be white.
Can you do it?
Okay?
Can I?
What are you putting away?
Okay, okay.
Ask Maria Jersey.
Uh, which way?
This way?
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
So we were number six.
Oh!
So can we go another first place?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
That was fast!
Fifth place! Fifth place for sure!
Suddenly!
Fifth place, please!
Okay, I'll go for number five.
I'm ready.
Okay, then. Fifth place.
Fifth place goes to...
Akane.
Oh!
Yay!
What kind of yay?
It was a very subtle yay.
Which way did it fall?
It's in the middle.
Um...
I'm one of the members, so my luck is pretty high.
My natural intuition, inspiration, and senses are sharpened.
So, I can notice something unusual among the members, or I can tell them that they need to fix something here.
You will be able to see things more easily, including things that need to be fixed.
So the luck itself is not that bad.
Just be careful how you choose your words.
There is a possibility of saying too much straight and hurting them.
It's just an indication.
So the luck itself is quite high.
I usually talk like a mother.
And next year, it's going to come out more.
I want you to do your homework.
I want you to do your homework, but there's a chance I'm gonna have to push you harder because it's gonna come out.
I'll be careful.
Yeah, well, I'm probably saving it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if anything happened.
I'm just kind of holding back what I want to say.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm probably hoarding.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Next, in fourth place...
Wakana.
Yes, she said it's basically stable.
That's what she said.
She says you can't tell what she's thinking from her facial expression.
But she can be as emotional as her facial expression.
If she's in a bad mood, she's in a bad mood.
If she's in a good mood, she's in a good mood, and if I say she's feeling good...
It makes it easier to understand things that are usually hard to understand.
It's like I'm playing the role of a mother.
Aaaaah!
Easy to understand
Easy to understand.
Koharu is already called a baby.
I'm sure.
It's just a matter of luck.
Maybe she'll grow up a little.
I see.
I'll be in high school.
I'll be an adult, and I'll be able to balance my surroundings.
And adjusting to the awkwardness in the air between each other's respective members.
It's amazing!
You're able to spend your time in such a peaceful way.
It's amazing how calm you can be.
And the theme
Yes.
Self-improvement, like pursuing cuteness or coolness.
It's better to have a theme of how to improve your strengths.
It's good to keep it in your mind. It's good to keep it in your mind.
I'll put it in my head. I'll put it in my head.
I'll try it in 2025.
I won't do it.
I'll do it.
Then number three.
Wow.
I'm in the podium.
There's the bottom line.
In third place...
Mr. Yuki.
Wow!
What's going on?
A little like Akane, she has a very refined sensibility,
I can see things from a very high position,
Oh, you see things like that?
Because I look at things from the top.
So I can guide people who might be going in the wrong direction.
I can see things from a very high position.
He goes for the atmosphere.
That's why I stand out more.
So they are in a position where they can be seen more.
But it's true that Koharu and others
She moves around freely.
That's what I often say.
I tell them, "Don't touch this part.
That's why it's good.
I'm always telling them what they shouldn't do.
You mean it comes out to people other than Koharu?
They tell me.
They might say that about us, too.
We have to do it right.
It's not just their point of view.
They'll see other things too.
This is the only thing I'm conscious of right now.
Just here.
Is it just here?
I can see so much more.
You can see so much more.
The branching itself will be much higher.
It's looking good right now.
As for the theme...
Eye care.
Wow!
You do that every day, don't you?
Eye drops!
I do exactly what I want with my eye drops.
You should keep doing that.
Try some sunglasses.
Sunglasses?
I bought these last year.
I bought these sunglasses this year.
Oh, those?
Those?
You already have them ready.
For my eyes.
So I don't have to look at my phone all the time.
Oh.
If you play video games...
You can reduce the amount of time you spend playing games.
You can watch a lot of dramas.
If you're logging in, reduce the amount of time you spend on your phone.
You just raised your right hand.
Oh, no.
I wear glasses at home.
They don't match my eyesight at all.
But it's a hassle to go out and buy them.
It's such a hassle to go out and buy them.
I've been neglecting them for more than three years.
I've been neglecting them for more than 3 years.
Should I do this next year?
No, I've already done it.
Ha-ha-ha.
You didn't.
Oh, this year? This one.
What if we don't do it next time?
Or next year.
That's what I'm talking about.
We'll do it this year. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll buy your glasses right now.
Thank you very much.
Who's left?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh.
I have no idea.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
I'm going to continue.
Followed by
Second place.
Mr. Serizawa!
Wow!
Toys.
Toys!
What is it?
What do you care?
It's gonna be so popular.
Yeah!
Yay!
I'm so excited!
Really?
We're talking about next year, right?
Yes, we're talking about 2025.
It comes once every 9 years.
Nine years?
That's when you'll be popular and get a lot of attention.
Oh, wow, that's the year I turn 20!
I see!
For example, if you introduce something, or say something about this outfit, it will spread and get a lot of attention.
You are an influencer.
Yes.
I say, "It's going to appear.
Wow!
That's amazing!
LOL!
I think it's okay to be so-so and free.
Heeeee!
Free to do what you want without being tied down.
And the members around you support you.
And the members around me will support me on their own.
In a manner of speaking.
That's right.
They do it on their own.
That's how it's going to be.
It's better to do as you please.
So I think it's better for the members to do as much as possible.
I think it's better to let the upper management
I think it's better to let them do as much as they want to do.
If they were freer...
That's right.
Do you want to hear the theme?
I'd like to hear about the theme.
Do you use fragrance? Perfume.
I use it a lot.
I'm wearing it today.
And then this scent that I already have...
It's an item.
One more thing.
I'd like to add a new scent.
You mean with the scent you're using now?
And one more thing.
You mean mix it with something else?
You can mix it or not, it's up to you.
I see.
Here, put on some perfume.
Not just perfume.
For example, you can change the scent of your body soap.
Bath salts.
Hand cream.
or bath salts.
It's very good.
Yes, sir.
And if you're going to specify a scent, citrus scents are the best.
I've never used citrus.
If you do that, it will make a big difference, or it will be more popular.
Let's use it.
I'll buy it.
I'll buy the next one.
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
I'm going.
Which one?
We're going to go for number one, okay?
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, first place goes to...
Mr. Miyazawa.
Yay!
That's great!
He's on a roll!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
You're doing great?
And I'm having great luck at work.
I've been thinking about what I want to do, what I want to do, what I want to do.
I can see what I want to do, but I can't move.
I've been having this imbalance between my feelings and my actions.
But now it's going to be aligned.
I'll be able to run faster and faster.
Wow, I'm shaking right now!
I'm shaking right now!
So cute!
She's just really pushing forward.
Heh! I get it!
He said to go fast, and if you really go forward, you'll stand out more and more.
Oh! I can run!
Please run!
So really, there's almost nothing to say.
Wow! That's good!
Great sensibility!
I guess I'll just have to get up early for the theme.
Oh, no! Wait, that's crazy! Lately!
I used to be good at getting up tomorrow, but lately I'm not so good in the morning.
Oh, man.
I can't get up at all.
You can do it next year.
That's for sure.
I'll start preparing for it this year.
I'll start preparing this year.
Prepare for it.
Right, right, right.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
Okay.
If you can't get up early, you can sleep in twice and get up once.
Oh, my God.
So I can get up tomorrow?
Is there a specific time I should get up?
Um...
It's, uh... it's my job.
My job, school...
I have a lot of things to do.
I'm good at using numbers to open doors.
Set your alarm for one minute.
One minute?
Like 1 minute to the hour.
7:01, 6:01, 8:01...
Each of us has our own lifestyle.
I'll wake up with an alarm once.
I mean, I wake up at 1:00 a.m. and go back to sleep.
It's really okay to sleep twice.
But you have to take the sunrise once.
So you wake up at, say, 7:01.
You open the curtains, take two sunrises, close the curtains, and then go back to sleep.
And then close the curtains and go back to sleep, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
What? 7:31 is okay?
Why all of a sudden?
Awww...
Oh, if there's a minute on the clock, I'm awake, right?
But 7:31 is a good number too, so 31.5.
Okay, I'll get up at 7:01.
I'll be up at 7:01.
What is it?
Which is it?
31?
I'll get up at 6:31.
Okay, one minute.
Okay, I'll do it.
But whatever.
Oh, my God, there's this really popular guy.
Someone who's willing to do whatever it takes to get you up.
I already said that.
I'm sorry. Seventh place.
I'm Hime...
I wonder...
What's wrong, Hime?
I'm Hime-chan.
I am Hime-chan
What's wrong?
I don't really want to rank them, but I got the data in advance, and I'm going to talk about it in the latter part of the interview, but the stroke count of my name itself is perfect.
Wow!
That's how I feel about it....
I see.
Well, that's because it's true. Even if the ranking is 7th, it is still 7th,
I think I will be able to see what I should do.
I am sure that I will be able to properly build up what I am lacking in the true sense of the word.
And first and foremost, I need to keep myself in good physical condition.
Yes.
I wonder if it is because of a mental breakdown.
I had a high fever in October of this year, and I had been hurt by that, and I was also prone to physical breakdowns, so I had to take care of that.
I like languages, while keeping the theme of taking good care of my physical condition.
Languages....
Korean, English, whatever.
Not so much.
Western music, Korean....
I don't care if it's a Western song, a Korean song.... Whatever it is, just leave it as it is.
In the language. Not the Japanese version,
I'm going to learn an American Western scatman's song.
Should I be able to sing?
If you say "Scatman" now, there is probably a generation, and no one....
And I don't know what Scatman is saying all the time.
It's very difficult.
It doesn't have to be scatman.
I don't care if it's Western music or the popular Hanriustan songs,
I sometimes listen to foreign songs.
I can listen to it and sing it as it is.
If you can do that, the atmosphere itself will be much more stable.
Then I went on to the key man, who was also a flautist.
What? Oh, no, not Flaus.
He is also a key man.
What do you mean?
He's the calmest guy in the group.
So he's not going to go off the rails to some extent.
But there's bound to be some rough spots.
And you're supposed to be able to calm them down.
Or control it.
A real adult in the true sense of the word.
Yes.
The key point is whether or not you can be an adult in the true sense of the word. So, I think it is better to be calm when everyone is making a fuss.
I think it would be good if I could do this. In addition, there is a possibility that you may get sick at a critical moment.
So that's all I have to say. I am in perfect physical condition.
That is our first priority. As long as you do that, you should be OK.
Take care of everyone.
Ease their burdens. I will do my best. I will, too. If you work too hard, you will become a nongoer.
Don't overdo it. Now that's the right expression. I will not force myself.
I will not push myself too hard. It would be better to be in a position to say, "I'm not going to push myself too hard," in 2025.
As a group.
Including a sense of stability. He is a key person who can be pushed to the limit.
I've seen this on other channels.
Did you have any lucky items for the group?
Just in case... what should we do with the group's items?
What do you want? Numbers, colors.
You got a "Yay", didn't you?
I got a "Yay".
If we're talking colors, our group color is pink right now.
But next year it will be pink.
It's our lucky color for 2025.
We are very careful about food and we like food a lot, but we like food a lot.
I like to eat food that's good for the group... like kiwi or bananas.
I like to eat things that are good for the group, like kiwi, banners, white rice, and maybe green peppers before a concert.
It changes every year, but...
I don't know what to do.
Maybe I should be a little more excited... maybe a drink?
Oh, I want to know!
I want to know!
A pre-game drink.
Sugar's good.
Oh!
A little sweet.
I need something sweet.
Something with honey.
Oh!
Something with honey!
Acerola juice with honey.
Oh!
Lemon juice with honey.
Can I have some yogurt with honey?
Yes!
Wow!
You can drink something with honey before a concert.
I'll do it.
Let's do it!
I can receive the energy of the people who have gathered
and give it back to them.
And it's going to be fruitful.
It has this characteristic.
That's why honey.
Wow!
Honey.
It's good for your throat.
Do you want a stage drink?
Honey.
Sure, sure, sure.
I like it!
Just like that.
Next year will be our 10th year as a group, and I'd like to know the best month for next year.
As a group, what month would be best for us?
Sure, there's a chance we can have a one-man show there.
That's for sure, that's for sure.
Our first show was in August, on August 1st.
I was going to say April, but now that I have that information, I'll change it.
April is really good.
Eeeee! Birthday!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I often think of it as a personal choice.
I'd rather have July than August.
July?
My birthday!
Well, if it's your birthday.
Birthday month.
Birthday months are unlucky.
Ehhhh!
Low energy.
Is that common?
I have that in common with you. All of you have that in common.
I have low energy too.
That's why I get energy from everyone saying congratulations.
So, in that sense, I guess it's a good thing.
I think it's good to have a concert in August, my birthday month, and to get congratulations from everyone.
It's nice to get congratulations from everyone.
I'm in a state of physical exhaustion, so as long as I can stay healthy there, I think it's OK.
Are you going to be okay with the month after your birthday?
The month after the birthday is over...
The month after the birthday is fine?
Is the second half of the month okay?
We only took care of the month of birth in the batch.
For example, if a person was born on August 1st
I've already received a birthday gift, so the remaining 30 days are fine.
something like that.
I've been told so many times.
It's a huge mistake, birthdays.
Yeah, I'm thinking that's probably it.
I'm thinking that maybe that's it.
I told him to be careful when he congratulates me...
April, July, August.
July? August is a good month for him. For him.
Thank you very much.
I guess we'll call it a wrap.
Yes, ma'am.
Shime, what did you think of the various readings?
Well, I came in 7th place.
Well, I hope that 2025 will lead to 2026.
I would like to do my best so that walkers can spread their wings even further.
I hope to do my best.
I am very happy that you gave me so much advice.
Thank you very much.
How did you do? I came in sixth, but I realized how important green peppers are to me.
Again? I've been thinking about it for a while... that I'm sorry I can't eat them, but I'm not good at them.
I'm going to try to like them from now on, and I'm also going to do my best so that at the end of 2025, I can say that I'm Luli Blue, a bell bell pepper lover.
That's it?
Yes.
I'll be back on your channel for the second half of the show, so I'll see you all there.
That's all for now.